Look at this picture, Felipe.
Посмотри на эту фотографию, Фелипе
Who are they?
Кто они?
This is my family.
Это моя семья.
This is my dad, his name is John.
Это мой папа, его зовут Джон.
And this is my mom, her name is Mary.
А это – моя мама, её зовут Мэри.
Who is this boy?
Кто этот мальчик?
This is my younger brother Evan. He's nine years old.
Это мой младший брат Эван. Ему 9 лет.
Do you have any other brothers or sisters?
У тебя есть другие братья или сёстры?
Yes. This one here is my older sister, she's twenty seven years old.
Да. Вот это здесь – моя старшая сестра, ей 27 лет.
She is pretty. Is she single?
Она симпатичная. Она не замужем?
No, she's married. The man behind her is her husband. His name is Thomas.
Нет, она замужем. Мужчина за ней – её муж. Его зовут Томас.
- What a pity! - Why?
- Как жаль! - Почему?
Nothing, nothing. What a beautiful family!
Не имеет значения, не имеет значения. Какая прекрасная семья.